Guide to the ILR School Communications Department Publications 1996-2018
ILR School Communications Department Publications
- Other ILR-Related Cornell Publications, 1996-2013; Undated; Communications, 2014-, Publication (Box 3)
  - MPS Program: New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Item 2: MPS Program New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Item 3: MPS Program New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - McPherson Honors and Awards Dinner, 2014; Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: McPherson Honors & Awards Dinner, Publication (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Professional Programs, New York City, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Cornell University ILR School Professional Programs: New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Cornell University ILR School. Spring. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Cornell University ILR School Professional Programs: New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; Spring. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Cornell University ILR School Professional Programs: New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 28)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3; Spring. Item is in English.
  - Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: The Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 2: The Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 3: The Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 4: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 5: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 6: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 7: Cornell Labor Arbitrator Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Item 8: Managing Organizational Conflict, Publication (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 4: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 5: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Item 6: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    The Judge William B. Groat Alumni Award: Sara Horowitz the Jerome Alpern Award: Beth C. Florin
    - Item 1: Groat & Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 2: Groat & Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: Groat & Alpern Awards 2015, Publication (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - ILR Conference Center Flyer, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Item 2: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Item 3: ILR Conference Center in King-Shaw Hall, Publication (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Managing Organizational Conflict, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Managing Organizational Conflict, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Item 2: Managing Organizational Conflict, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Item 3: Managing Organizational Conflict, Publication (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Master of Industrial and Labor Relations (MILR), 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Master of Industrial Labor Relations (MILR), Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Item 2: Master of Industrial Labor Relations (MILR), Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Item 3: Master of Industrial and Labor Relations (MILR), Publication (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Maximize Your Leadership Potential, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Item 1: Maximize your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Item 2: Maximize your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Item 3: Maximize your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Professional Neutral Development Program, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Item 2: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Item 3: Professional Neutral Development Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Professional Programs in New York City, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Item 2: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; spring. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3; spring. Item is in English.
    - Item 4: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
      By Cornell University ILR School. fall. Item is in English.
    - Item 5: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; fall. Item is in English.
    - Item 6: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 37)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3; fall. Item is in English.
  - Public Engagement, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Public Engagement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Item 2: Public Engagement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Item 3: Public Engagement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: Cornell University's Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Item 2: Cornell University's Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Item 3: Cornell University's Scheinman Institute on Conflict Resolution, Publication (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - The Worker Institute, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Item 2: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Item 3: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
      By Cornell University ILR School. spring. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Item 4: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Item 5: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Item 6: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Diversity and Inclusion Certificate Program, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Diversity and Inclusion Certificate, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Item 2: Diversity and Inclusion Certificate, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Item 3: Diversity and Inclusion Certificate, Publication (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Employee Relations, Investigation and Employment Law Program, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: Employee Relations, Investigations and Employment Law, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Item 2: Employee Relations, Investigations and Employment Law, Publication (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Groat and Alpern Awards, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Groat & Alpern Invitation, Sponsorship, Prereception Reservation Cards, Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Item 2: Groat & Alpern Invitation, Sponsorship, Prereception Reservation Cards, Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Item 3: Groat & Alpern Invitation, Sponsorship, Prereception Reservation Cards, Publication (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Leadership Essentials Certificate Program, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Item 2: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Item 3: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Professional Programs, New York City, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 2: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 3: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 4: Cornell ILR School Prodessional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 5: Cornell ILR School, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 6: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 7: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Item 8: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
      By Cornell University ILR School. flyer. Item is in English.
    - Item 9: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; flyer. Item is in English.
    - Item 10: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 46)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 3; flyer. Item is in English.
  - The Worker Institute, 2016; Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Item 2: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Item 3: The Worker Institute: Advancing Worker Rights and Collective Representation, Publication (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Advance, ILR Alumni Magazine, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 48)
    Fall 2017
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Leadership Essential Certificate Flyer, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: Be the Next Generation Leader for Your Organization, Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Item 2: Be the Next Generation Leader for Your Organization, Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Item 3: Be the Next Generation Leader for Your Organizatio, Publication (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Winter Intersession Program: Freshman Externship Program Flyer, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Winter Intersession Program Freshman Externship Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Item 2: Winter Intersession Program Freshman Externship Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Item 3: Winter Intersession Program Freshman Externship Program, Publication (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Cornell ILR School Professional Programs: New York City, 2017-2018; Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
    Fall 2017/Spring2018
    - Item 1: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Item 2: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Item 3: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Cornell ILR School Professional Programs: New York City flyer, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 52)
      By Cornell University ILR School. flyer; copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: Cornell ILR School Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 52)
      By Cornell University ILR School. flyer; copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Leadership Essentials Certificate Program flyer, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Item 2: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Item 3: Maximize Your Leadership Potential, Publication (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
    Spring 2017
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Item 2: Adb=vance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 54)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 2; spring 2017. Item is in English.
  - Cornell ILR School Professional Programs: New York City, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
    Spring/Fall 2017
    - Item 1: Professional Programs New Yorki City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Item 2: Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
      By Cornell University ILR School. copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: Professional Programs New York City, Publication (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - The Worker Institute, 2017; Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The Worker Institute, Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Item 2: The Worker Institute, Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Item 3: The Worker Institute, Publication (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2015; Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
    Fall 2015
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Advance: ILR Alumni Magazine, 2014; Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
    Fall 2014
    - Item 1: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Item 2: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Item 3: Advance ILR Alumni Magazine, Publication (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - ILR School: Public Engagement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: Public Engagement, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Item 2: Public Engagament, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Item 3: Public Engagament, Publication (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - The ILR School, 2010; Publication (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: The ILR School, Publication (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Item 2: The ILR School, Publication (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - ILR Alumni Magazine (Winter 2018), Publication (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Posters, Publication (Box 4)
  - "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks", 2015; Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Life and times of Harry Bridges. Performed by Ian Ruskin. February 19, 2015.
    - Item 1: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks": This one-man multimedia stage production on the life and times of legendary labor leader Harry Bridges, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Broadside. Item is in English.
    - Item 2: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks": This one-man multimedia stage production on the life and times of legendary labor leader Harry Bridges, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Broadside Copy 1. Item is in English.
    - Item 3: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks": This one-man multimedia stage production on the life and times of legendary labor leader Harry Bridges, Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
      By Cornell University School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Broadside Copy 2. Item is in English.
    - Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 5: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks", Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 6: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks", Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Item 7: "From Wharf Rats to Lords of the Docks", Publication (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - "Bowling Alone": Living Apart, But Working Together, 2015; Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Cynthia Estlund. Milton Konvitz Memorial Lecture, April 27, 2015.
    - Item 1: Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 2: Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 3: Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together, Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 4: "Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together", Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 5: "Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together", Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Item 6: "Bowling Alone, Living Apart, but Working Together", Publication (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - The Hand That Feeds, 2015; Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Showing of the documentary film. November 5, 2015.
    - Item 1: The Hand That Feeds an Award-Winning Documentary Film, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: The Hand That Feeds an Award-Winning Documentary Film, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 3: The Hand That Feeds an Award-Winning Documentary Film, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 4: The Hand That Feeds, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 5: The Hand That Feeds, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Item 6: The Hand That Feeds, Publication (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, 2015; Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Conference poster. Kristen Hopewell, Beverly Silver, Wendy Wolford. October 9-10, 2015.
    - Item 1: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 2: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 3: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 4: Labor, Capital, and South South Development: Emergeny Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 5: Labor, Capital, and South-South Development: Emergency Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Item 6: Labor, Capital, and South-South Development: Emergency Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Unconventional Responses to Unique Catastrophes: Tailoring the Law to Meet the Challenges, 2016; Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Kenneth R. Feinberg. Milton Konvitz Memorial Lecture, April 25, 2016.
    - Item 1: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 2: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 3: Labor, Capital and South-South Development: Emergent Polycentrism in the Global Economy, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 4: Unconventional Responses to Unique Catastrophes: Tailoring the Law to Meet the Challenges, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Item 5: Unconventional Responses to Unique Catastrophes: Tailoring the Law to Meet the Challenges, Publication (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Union Days 2017. "Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing, and Building Coalitions", 2014; Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing & Building Coalitions!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 2: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing & Building Coalitions!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 3: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing & Building Coalitions!, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 4: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing, and Building Coalitions, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 5: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing, and Building Coalitions, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Item 6: Fighting Back: Resisting, Organizing, and Building Coalitions, Publication (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Union Days 2018. "Subverting Technology: Radical Possibilities for the Future of Work", Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Subverting Technology: radical Possibilities for the Future of Work, Publication (Box 4, Folder 7)